const questions = [

    {
        questionText: 'What is the result of 2 + 2 in JavaScript?',
        choices: ['3', '4', '5', '6'],
        correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    
    {
        questionText: 'How do you declare a variable in JavaScript?',
        choices: ['var', 'let', 'const', 'all of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 3,
    },

    {
        questionText: 'What is the purpose of the JavaScript "alert" function?',
        choices: ['To display a message in the console', 'To display a popup alert box with a message', 'To create a new variable', 'To loop through an array'],
        correctAnswer: 1,
    },

    {
        questionText: 'Which operator is used for strict equality comparison in JavaScript?',
        choices: ['==', '===', '!=', '!=='],
        correctAnswer: 1,
    },

    {
        questionText: 'What does the "typeof" operator return for an array?',
        choices: ['object', 'array', 'string', 'number'],
        correctAnswer: 0,
    },

    {
        questionText: 'How do you comment out a single line in JavaScript?',
        choices: ['// This is a comment', '/* This is a comment */', '-- This is a comment', '## This is a comment'],
        correctAnswer: 0,
    },

    {
        questionText: 'What is the purpose of the "console.log" function in JavaScript?',
        choices: ['To perform mathematical calculations', 'To display data on the web page', 'To log messages to the browser console', 'To create HTML elements'],
        correctAnswer: 2,
    },

    {
        questionText: 'Which loop is used for iterating over the elements of an array in JavaScript?',
        choices: ['for loop', 'while loop', 'if statement', 'switch statement'],
        correctAnswer: 0,
    },

    {
        questionText: 'What is the result of the expression "5 + \'5\'" in JavaScript?',
        choices: ['10', '55', 'Error', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: 1,
    },

    {
        questionText: 'What keyword is used to define a function in JavaScript?',
        choices: ['function', 'define', 'method', 'class'],
        correctAnswer: 0,
    }

];
